cineworld.co.uk 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Cineworld Cinemas

### Your consent

By using our website (which includes our mobile site and any Cineworld approved apps) and providing us with your personal information you agree that we may collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Where you submit information (including information containing personal data) to us, you confirm that you have all necessary permissions and consents to do so and that you have read, and agree to, the terms of our Privacy Policy.

### What information do we collect and how do we use it?

By entering your personal information on the Cineworld web site and/or our Facebook booking app you agree that we may retain your information and it may be held by Cineworld or by any third party company which processes it on our behalf.

### General Bookings and purchases

#### Information we may collect from you

If you wish to book tickets using our website or otherwise, we will need to know some details about you such as your name, e-mail address and payment card details.   We may also need this information when you make any other purchases via our website, such as ordering food, drink or 3D glasses.  If you request a booking confirmation to be sent by SMS, we will also ask for you to provide your mobile phone number. 

If you contact us or have an enquiry we will also keep a record of this.

#### How we use this information

We gather this information to allow us, our agents and sub-contractors to process your booking, fulfill your orders and to send you service related emails (and where requested text messages) for your booking. 

We may also use these details to send you a follow-up email after your cinema visit, to check that you were satisfied with our service.  

### mycineworld

#### Information we may collect from you

If you wish to sign up to the mycineworld service, we will ask you to complete the registration process to register for an account.  As part of this process, we will ask for certain information such as your name and e-mail address.  You may also provide us with additional information when using your mycineworld account, for example to update your personal details through My Profile or to make purchases online. 

#### How we use this information

We gather this information to allow us, our agents and sub-contractors to provide you with this service including to facilitate your use of our Cineworld Advance Booking service.   This information is also used to identify you when you visit the website including to assist with logging in to your account. 

If you have given us your consent to do so, we also use this information to send to you emails and/or SMS highlighting our latest offers and promotions, weekly film times, upcoming attractions and information about special features of our website or any other service or products which we think may be of interest to you and for our other marketing related purposes.  Where you have asked us to, we will  securely store your payment card details, to help speed up the online booking process for you.

If at any time you decide you would rather not receive these emails or SMS, simply login to your mycineworld account, go to My Profile then My Newsletters and tick or un-tick the boxes next to the relevant newsletter or update or follow the instructions about how to unsubscribe at the end of each email.  To ask us to delete your stored payment card details simply login to your mycineworld account, go to My Profile then My Stored Cards and remove your card details as directed.   Alternatively, please phone us on 0844 815 7747 (or 0044 844 815 7747 if calling from Republic of Ireland) or email us at [customer.services@cineworld.co.uk](mailto:customer.services@cineworld.co.uk).

### Facebook Connect

If you sign up to mycineworld by using Facebook Connect via our Facebook page you will also be subject to Facebook's terms and conditions of use and Facebook's privacy policy which we recommend you read.  Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Facebook and Facebook's information practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

### Unlimited members

#### Information we may collect from you

If you join our Unlimited membership scheme we will ask you to complete the registration process to register for an account.  As part of this process, we will ask for certain information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, age, and depending on your choice of payment method, payment card and/or bank details.    We will also ask you to provide a photo of yourself for use on your Unlimited membership card. 

If you sign up for Unlimited membership for someone else (for example, if it is a gift), we will still need some information about you but we will also ask for the details of the person who will be the Unlimited member.   Where you submit information (including information containing personal data) to us, you confirm that you have all necessary permissions and consents to do so.   

#### How we use this information

We gather this information to allow us, our agents and sub-contractors to provide you with the Unlimited membership services including to communicate with you and/or the registered Unlimited member.  This information is used to identify you when you visit the website including to assist with logging in to your account.

If you have given us your consent to do so, we may also use this information to send to you (and/or the Unlimited member) our Unlimited newsletter and other communications containing information about your membership account, offers, products and/or services which we think may be of interest to you and for our other marketing related purposes.

If at any time you decide you would rather not receive these email, please contact the Unlimited Helpdesk on 0844 372 3445 (or 0818 304 204 if calling from Republic of Ireland), by email at [contactus@unlimitedcineworld.com](mailto:contactus@unlimitedcineworld.com) or follow the instructions about how to unsubscribe at the end of each email.  

### Other uses of our website

There may be other ways in which we collect and process your information when you visit our website, for example:

  * we may ask you to complete surveys for research purposes (although you do not have to respond to them).
  * details of your visits to our website (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data) and the pages that you access.
  * information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type for system administration. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual - please see our [Cookie Policy](http://www.cineworld.co.uk/cookies/about) for more details.

We may use this information to:

  * to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website.
  * to notify you about any changes to our website.

### External web sites

Our website may link to a number of external websites.  If you click on one of these links you acknowledge that your access of such websites will be subject to that website's own terms and conditions and privacy policy.  Cineworld has no control over how such information is used by these websites and, as such, any course of action you have regarding any alleged misuse of such information must be against the owners of the relevant website.  You acknowledge that the same information may be provided by you to both that website and Cineworld, but only when specifically provided to Cineworld is it subject to this Privacy Policy.  Please check the relevant terms and conditions and privacy policy before using such websites. 

### What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer. 

We use cookies to let you move around our website and use essential features such as our online ticket booking system.  We also use cookies to keep track of the pages you and other visitors to our website have viewed and to tell us whether you have visited the website previously in order to deliver a better service for example, to store information about your preferences and to identify you and allow us to efficiently operate our login service.  

The information we store within the cookie is encoded and restricted so only we (and our trusted third parties) are able to access this information. 

Please see our [Cookie Policy](http://www.cineworld.co.uk/cookies/about) for more information on how we use cookies, and how you can adjust your cookie settings.  Note that if you decline our cookies or ask for notification each time a cookie is being sent, this may affect your ease of use of our website.

### How does Cineworld protect customer information?

While the nature of the Internet is such that we cannot guarantee the security of the information you transmit to us via the Internet, we follow strict security procedures (including appropriate technical and organisational measures) in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access or loss.  Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to discuss your account details or other queries.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.  We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

### Will Cineworld disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

We may share your information in the following circumstances:

  * If you enter a competition on our website or through our Facebook app, we may pass your details on to third parties for the purposes of administering the competition and/or delivering prizes.
  * To other members of our group, our partners and service providers (such as our agents and sub-contractors) for the purpose of managing or administering certain aspects of our website, or to help us develop new services.
  * If you have given us your consent to do so, we may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If subsequently you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, please contact our Customer Services team by phone on (0844 815 7747 or 0044 844 815 7747 if calling from Republic of Ireland) or by email at [customer.services@cineworld.co.uk](mailto:customer.services@cineworld.co.uk). 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation and/or in order to enforce or apply any other agreements between you and us.
  * Where we are obliged to, or permitted to do so, by law, court order or to comply with any search warrant or similar presented to Cineworld by any to law enforcement or government officer.
  * In the event that our business is sold or integrated with another business your information may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers' advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.
  * we may provide aggregate statistics about you, our other customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics will be anonymous and not include any personal identifying information.

### Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  This information is aggregated and anonymous information and does not include personally identifiable information. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices over having this information used by these companies please see our [Cookie Policy](http://www.cineworld.co.uk/cookies/about) or contact us at [feedback@cineworld.co.uk](mailto:feedback@cineworld.co.uk).

### Updating, Verifying and Deleting Personal Data

You may inform us of any changes in your information. In accordance with our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998, we will update or delete your information accordingly. To find out what information we hold about you or to have your information updated, amended or removed from our database, please email us at [customer.services@cineworld.co.uk](mailto:customer.services@cineworld.co.uk).  Any such data subject access requests may be subject to a small admin fee.

### Tell us what you think

Cineworld welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please call us on 0844 815 7747 (or 0044 844 815 7747 if calling from Republic of Ireland) or e-mail us at [customer.services@cineworld.co.uk](mailto:customer.services@cineworld.co.uk).
